Guide to the Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Tuol Sleng confessions and photographs, 1991-1993
4883
215 reels microfilm, 5 albums
Microfilm Reels.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Transcripts of confessions obtained from prisoners at Tuol Sleng Prison, Phnom Penh, Cambodia. Also, five thousand photographs of Tuol Sleng prisoners.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Transcripts of confessions obtained from prisoners at Tuol Sleng Prison, Phnom Penh, Cambodia. Also, five thousand photographs of Tuol Sleng prisoners.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.--Library.--Echols Collection.; Tuol Sleng Museum of Genocide (Phnom Penh, Cambodia).
Places:
Cambodia.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
PROVENANCE
The records in this collection were filmed under the direction of the Cornell University Library's John M. Echols Collection on Southeast Asia and the Department of Conservation and Preservation at the Tuol Sleng museum of Genocide in Phnom Penh, Cambodia, from January 1991 to April 1993. The confessions of some 4300 detainees comprising 400,000 pages of handwritten text in Khmer, as well as internal prison documents were filmed. This project was part of a larger effort to preserve and film Cambodian manuscripts at five locations in Phnom Penh.
RELATED MATERIAL
See also: Guide to Cambodia Documentation Commission Records (collection #4499)
See also: Yale University Cambodian Genocide Program Database for more detailed information about what is on our microfilm. To use this database for materials from this collection, search under "Sources" for "Tuol Sleng Catalogue of Confessions".
SERIES LIST
The references are listed in alphabetical order by detainees' given names.
Each reference includes a microfilm reel number and item number (frame) indicating the order by which the confessions appear on the reels.
If available, the age, gender, entry dates (in the date column), confession dates, and nationality are also listed.
Series I. Confessions A-E, H
Names: A
Names: B
Names: C
Names: D
Names: E
Names: H
Series II. Confessions I-N
Names: I
Names: J
Names: K
Names: L
Names: M
Names: N
Series III. Confessions O-S
Names: O
Names: P
Names: Q
Names: R
Names: S
Names: Sa
Names: Sb-Se
Names: Si
Names: So
Names: Sr
Names: Su-Sy
Series IV. Confessions T-V, Y
Names: T
Names: U
Names: V
Names: Y
Series V. Other Microfilm Reels
Series VI. Photograph Albums
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Confessions A-H (No F or G), Dates are formatted as Day/Month/Year
  - Names: A
    - Ab Dulla, 11/4/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 14)
      Sex: male
      Age: 36
      Dates of Confessions: N/A
      Nationality (if foreign): Unknown
    - Agis Halima ( India ), 11/4/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 18)
      Age: N/A
    - Agy Issak Kany, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 20)
      Sex: female
      Age: 20
    - Agy Sara Byby, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 19)
      Age: 23
    - Agy Skarim, N/A (Reel 185, Frame 21)
      Age: 18
    - Ai Chuy, 41/2/1978 (Reel 2, Frame 10)
      Age: 25
    - Ai Run, N/A (Reel N/A, Frame N/A)
      Sex: N/A
      Age: 58
    - Aing Ban Hok, 11/3/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 1)
      Age: 45
      Dates of Confessions: 11/4/1977(2); 3/4/1977
    - Aing Chou By, N/A (Reel 2, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/12/1975
    - Am Chhum, 29/2/1976 (Reel 2, Frame 15)
    - Am Em, 15/5/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 2)
      Age: 31
      Dates of Confessions: 15/5/1977
    - Am Im, 4/2/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 4)
      Age: 27
    - Am Sokhon, 5/4/1976 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
      Age: 24
      Dates of Confessions: 15/4/1978; 27/4/1978; 1/5/1978; 5/5/1978; 7/5/1978; 14/5/1978
    - An Hov, 1/8/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/9/1977
    - An Khun, 5/5/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 19)
      Age: 22
      Dates of Confessions: 3/9/1976;4/9/1976(5); 5/9/1976(2); 6/9/1976(2); 7/9/1976(4); 1 section undated
    - An Kim Ann, N/A (Reel 2, Frame 5)
      Age: 26
    - An Maung, 28/6/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 12)
      Age: 30
      Dates of Confessions: 24/9/1977; 8/7/1977; 3/7/1977
    - An Seng Heang, 12/15/1976 (Reel 1, Frame 3)
      Age: 29
      Dates of Confessions: 15/12/1976; 22/12/1976; 23/12//1976; 31/12/1976; 3/1/1977
      6/10/1/1977; 20/1/1977; /1977; 24/1/1977; 25/1/1977; 28/1/1977; 3/2/1977; 4/2/1977
      11/2/1977; 15/2/1977; 19/2/1977; 20/2/1977; 21/2/1977; 25/2/1977; 26/2/1977
      27/2/1977; 4/3/1977; 5/3/1977; 3/8/1977; 9/3/1977
    - An Yun, N/A (Reel 2, Frame 3)
      Age: 49
      Dates of Confessions: 5/6/1978; 25/4/1978
    - Ang Kan, 26/9/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/10/1977; 9/11/1977
    - Ang Saroeurn, N/A (Reel 2, Frame 21)
      Age: 28
      Dates of Confessions: 17/7/1976; 20/7/1976; 23/7/1976; 24/8/1976; 28/8/1976; 25/8/1976
    - Ann Sras, 3/2/1977 (Reel 1, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/4/1977; 4/4/1977
    - Aou Yok Siv, 7/5/1976 (Reel 2, Frame 8)
    - Ath Khat, 5/6/1978 (Reel 2, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/8/1978
    - Aum Srim, 27/7/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1977; 10/10/1977
    - Aung Sokhom, N/A (Reel 2, Frame 22)
      Age: 34
      Dates of Confessions: 3 sections undated; 3/2/1977; 4/2/1977; 5/2/1977
    - Ay Ho, 13/2/1978 (Reel 2, Frame 18)
      Age: 33
      Dates of Confessions: 17/2/1978; 28/2/1978
    - Ay Kan, 12/16/1976 (Reel 2, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/12/1976; 27/17/1976; 3/1/1977(2); 4/1/1977(2); 24/1/1977(2)
    - Ay Sbo, N/A (Reel 2, Frame 9)
      Age: 35
      Dates of Confessions: 25/2/1977; 10/3/1977; 7/3/1977; 4/3/1977; 11/3/1977
      26/3/1977; 27/4/1977; 30/4/1977; 5/5/1977
    - Ay That, 10/1977 (Reel 2, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/8/1977; 13/9/1977; 4/10/1977
  - Names: B
    - Ban Buoy, 3/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/4/1977; 24/3/1977
    - Ban Chhan, 1/8/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/9/1977; 12/9/1977; 4/10/1977
    - Ban Sarin, 26/10/1975 (Reel 4, Frame 37)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/11/1977
    - Ban Saroeurn, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/2/1978
    - Bas Peng Kheang, 18/1/1976 (Reel 4, Frame 13)
      Age: 32
    - Bav Vann, 30/5/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/5/1977
    - Be Meng Heng, 27/10/1975 (Reel 3, Frame 32)
      Age: 19
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1977; 3/11/1976; 3/1/1976
    - Ben Roeurn, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 10)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/9/1976
    - Ben Tan Hangsa, 12/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1978
    - Beng, 23/3/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/3/1977
    - Beng Hong, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 19)
      Age: 42
      Dates of Confessions: 24/1/1978
    - Beng Pum, 6/11/1975 (Reel 4, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/11/1975
    - Beng Soeurn, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/7/1977
    - Bin Ban, 1/6/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/8/1977; 20/9/1977; 10/9/1977; 18/8/1977; 5/8/1977; 11/9/1977; 23/4/1977
      20/4/1977; 22/4/1977; 10/8/1977; 20/9/1977; 11/8/1977
    - Bin Prok, 27/10/1978 (Reel 3, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/11/1978
    - Bin Saroeurn, 6/10/1975 (Reel 4, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/1/1976
    - Bin Sorn, 10/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/2/1978
    - Bin Yeang, 11/12/1976 (Reel 3, Frame 28)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/1/1977; 17/12/1976; 8/1/1977; 23/12/1976; 3/1/1977
    - Bith Phat, 9/12/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/2/1978
    - Bo Poun, 16/1/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/2/1978 / 25/2/1978/ 26/2/1978
    - Boeurn, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 22)
    - Boeurn Moeurn, 13/7/1977 (Reel 125, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/8/1977; 23/8/1977; 1/8/1977; 13/9/1977; 21/7/1977(2)
    - Boeurn Out, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/8/1977
    - Boeurn Rom, 27/6/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/9/1977
    - Bong Son, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 40)
    - Bor Yorn, 12/9/1976 (Reel 4, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/7/1978
    - Born Nan, 20/3/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 1)
      Age: 39
      Dates of Confessions: 10/4/1978; 11?4/1978; 3/5/1978
    - Bou Chhean, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 17)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/9/1976
    - Bou Eam, 11/3/1976 (Reel 4, Frame 31)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/3/1976
    - Bou Keo, 3/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 27)
      Age: 40
      Dates of Confessions: 12/7/1977
    - Bou Khorn, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/1/1977
    - Bou Ngorn Ly, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 18)
      Age: 17
    - Bou Phally, 26/7/1975 (Reel 4, Frame 23)
      Age: 21
      Dates of Confessions: 26/7/1975
    - Bou Phat, 3/1/1978 (Reel 3, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1978(2); 28/1/1978; 29/1/1978; 5/2/1978; 13/2/1978; 21/2/1978
      25/2/1978; 10/4/1978; 4 sections undated
    - Bou Pheak, 11/1/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/2/1977
    - Bou Rom, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/21/1977; 4/9/1977
    - Bou Samut, 10/7/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/3/1978
    - Bou Savin, 5/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 3)
    - Bou Sean, 15/1/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 39)
    - Bou Vith, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 14)
    - Boun Hok, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 17)
    - Boun Navi, 9/12/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/12/1977
    - Bour Minthor, 29/12/1975 (Reel 4, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/12/1975
    - Bour Seang Hong, 30/6/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/7/1978
    - Bouy (Bony) Vinh Vy, 1/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 72)
      Nationality (if foreign): Vietnam
    - Bouy Hong Ve, N/A (Reel 186, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/11/1978; 15/11/1978
    - Bov Hor Seng, 9/6/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/7/1978
    - Boy Boeurn, 1/2/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/2/1978; 3/2/1978; 10/4/1978
    - Bui Van Hiu, N/A (Reel 186, Frame 24)
    - Bun Beang, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 19)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/7/1977
    - Bun Chhean Sroul, 4/3/1978 (Reel 3, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/4/1978; 4/4/1978; 15/4/1978
    - Bun Kong, 2/6/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/8/1977; 15/8/1977; 14/8/1977; 15/9/1977; 30/4/1978
    - Bun Long, 6/8/1975 (Reel 3, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/9/1975; 10/9/1975; 5/9/1975; 6/9/1975; 9/9/1975
      7/7/1975; 23 sections undated
    - Bun Nary, 8/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 38)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/8/1977; 17/9/1977; 1 section undated
    - Bun Nuon, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: No date
    - Bun Phavy (Phauy), 9/4/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 12)
      Nationality (if foreign): Takeo
    - Bun Ra, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/2/1977
    - Bun Saay, 7/5/1976 (Reel 4, Frame 41)
    - Bun Sany, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/5/1976; 10/7/1976; 11/7/1976; 11/7/1975; 15/7/1976
      18/7/1976; 21/7/1976; 23/7/1976; 26/7/1976; 27/7/1976; 7/1976
    - Bun Seng 2, 8/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/1977
    - Bun Song, 29/12/1975 (Reel 3, Frame 5)
      Age: 44
    - Bun Thaang, 24/7/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 35)
    - Bun Thea, 12/10/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1/1977
    - Bun Thoeurng, N/A (Reel 186, Frame 59)
    - Bun Ye, 1/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 36)
    - Bunnarak, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/10/1975
    - Buon Than, 2/2/1978 (Reel 3, Frame 10)
      Age: 54
      Dates of Confessions: 6/2/1978
    - Buoy Sreng, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 8)
    - But Mol, 15/12/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/12/1978; 22/12/1978
    - But Nev, 16/6/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 34)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/6/1977
    - But Phat, 12/1/1976 (Reel 4, Frame 8)
    - Buth Aum, 20/1/1978 (Reel 4, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/2/1978; 17/2/1978; 2 sections undated
    - Buth Ban, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/7/19771
    - Buth Han, 29/8/1977 (Reel 3, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/8/1977; 29/8/1977; 19/9/1977
    - Buth Heng, 4/5/1978 (Reel 3, Frame 24)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/5/1978
    - Buth Moeuk, 23/11/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/1/1978
    - Buth Yan, N/A (Reel 3, Frame 7)
    - Buy Suos, N/A (Reel 4, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/1/1978
    - By Sambo, 21/1/1978 (Reel 3, Frame 20)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/2/1978; 5/2/1978
  - Names: C
    - Can' Sorn, 13/8/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 17)
      Age: 50
      Dates of Confessions: 13/9/1978
    - Cao Chrech, 27/8/1976 (Reel 152, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 3/9/1976; 23/9/1976
    - Chak Chea, 23/6/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/6/1977
    - Chak Huot, N/A (Reel 13, Frame 15)
    - Chak On, 23/3/1976 (Reel 20, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/5/1977
    - Chak Oun, N/A (Reel 11, Frame 3)
    - Chan Chakrey, 19/5/1976 (Reel 15, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/1976; 1/6/1976; 14/6/1976; 22/6/1976; 7/1976; 3/7/1976; 7/7/1976
      9/7/1976; 10/7/1976; 11/7/1976; 13/7/1976; 14/7/1976; 15/7/1976; 16/7/1976; 17/7/1976; 18/7/1976
      19/8/1976; 21/7/1976; 22/7/1976; 24/7/1976; 25/7/1976; 27/7/1976; 28/7/1976; 28/7/1976; 29/7/1976
      30/7/1976; 31/7/1976; 8/1976; 2/8/1976; 3/8/1976; 6/8/1976; 8/8/1976; 9/8/1976; 13/8/1976
    - Chan Chan, 27/5/1978 (Reel 12, Frame 23)
      Age: 41
      Dates of Confessions: 3/6/1978; 4/6/1978; 23//6/1978
    - Chan Chheang, 25/1/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/2/1978
    - Chan Chhom, 3/10/1975 (Reel 16, Frame 12)
    - Chan Chhom, 30/1/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 2)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/9/1977
    - Chan Choeurn, 16/8/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/8/1977; 21/8/1977
    - Chan Han, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 24)
    - Chan Hoeurn, N/A (Reel 6, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/10/1977; 9/10/1976; 10/10/1976; 11/10/1976; 12/10/1976; 13/10/1976; 14/10/1976; 15/10/1976
      16/10/1976; 3/11/1976; 4/11/1976; 5/11/1976; 6/11/1976; 7/11/1976; 19/11/1976
      20/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 22/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 24/11/1976; 25/11/1976; 26/11/1976
      27/11/1976; 28/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 30/11/1976
    - Chan Kean, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 6)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/11/1975
    - Chan Kham, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 43)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/5/1977
    - Chan Kim, 8/12/1978 (Reel 21, Frame 26)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/12/1978; 17/12/1978; 19/12/1978; 20/12/1978
      24/12/1978; 9/12/1978; 16/12/1978
    - Chan Kolap, 6/1/1978 (Reel 185, Frame 13)
    - Chan Lan, 27/6/1978 (Reel 19, Frame 37)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/10/1978; 3/7/1978
    - Chan Lorn, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 16)
    - Chan Mao, 8/1978 (Reel 22, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/8/1978
    - Chan Mon, 28/2/1977 (Reel 13, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/3/1977; 26/3/1977; 27/3/1977; 4/5/1977; 7/4/1977; 11/6/1977
    - Chan Mony, N/A (Reel 16, Frame 2)
    - Chan Mut, 10/9/1978 (Reel 21, Frame 17)
      Age: 15
      Dates of Confessions: 27/9/1978
    - Chan Nak, N/A (Reel 11, Frame 16)
    - Chan Nhoung, N/A (Reel 6, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/2/1978; 19/2/1978 20/2/1978; 16/2/1978
    - Chan Nuon, 18/9/1976 (Reel 8, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/9/1976; 25/9/1976; 27/9/1976; 30/9/1976; 2/10/1976; 16/ 10/1976
      30/10/1976; 2/11/1976; 4/11/1976; 6/11/1976; 7/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 9/11/1976
      11/11/1976; 13; 11/1976; 15/11/1976; 16/11/1976; 18/11/1976; 19/11/1976; 20/11/1976
      22/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 23/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 25/11/1976
      1/12/1976; 2/1/1976
    - Chan Ny, 7/5/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 39)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1977
    - Chan Oeur, 30/10/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/12/1977
    - Chan Oeurn, 21/10/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/2/1977; 14/11/1977; 15/2/1978; 8/2/1978
    - Chan Phan, 27/7/1976 (Reel 13, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/8/1976; 26/8/1976
    - Chan Phat, 20/9/1977 (Reel 4, Frame 43)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/11/1977; 14/1/1978
    - Chan Pheng, 26/1/1978 (Reel 21, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 12/2/1978
    - Chan Phon, 16/4/1978 (Reel 16, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/5/1978; 23/4/1978; 18/4/1978; 27/4/1978
    - Chan Phy, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 29)
    - Chan Rey, 7/1/1977 (Reel 22, Frame 32)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/2/1977
    - Chan Rin, 30/1/1977 (Reel 23, Frame 4)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/2/1978
    - Chan Sam, 11/10/1978 (Reel 17, Frame 6)
      Age: 136
      Dates of Confessions: 2510/1977; 8/10/1978; 7/9/1978; 10/10/1978; 2 sections undated
    - Chan Sam At, 29/10/1977 (Reel 7, Frame 3)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/02/91
    - Chan San, 23/3/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 21)
    - Chan Sithan, 20/5/1976 (Reel 21, Frame 37)
    - Chan Sok, 24/1/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 15/3/1977;25/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 16/3/1977
      (2) 19/3/1977; 22/3/1977; 23/3/1977; 25/3/1977; 1 section undated
    - Chan Sothy, N/A (Reel 11, Frame 4)
    - Chan Sreang, 17/2/1977 (Reel 12, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/8/1977; 18/11/1977; 13/1/1978; 7/4/1978; 2 sections undated
    - Chan Srin, N/A (Reel 20, Frame 35)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/1/1977
    - Chan Synak, N/A (Reel 10, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/9/1976; 21/9/1976; 27/9/1976; 23/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 28/9/1976; 22/9/1976; 26/9/1976; 12/9/1976
    - Chan Than, 9/9/1978 (Reel 22, Frame 29)
    - Chan Thol, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/5/1977
    - Chan Thol, 26/2/1977 (Reel 23, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 8/3/1977; 10/3/1977; 17/3/1977; 20/3/1977
      25/3/1977; 29/3/1977; 31/3/1977; 17/5/1977
    - Chan Thy, 11/6/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/6/1977
    - Chan Uon, 29/6/1978 (Reel 19, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/7/1978
    - Chan Van, 27/12/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 41)
    - Chan Vann, 4/4/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/4/1977
    - Chan Yon, 21/10/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/8/1978
    - Chan You Run, 28/10/1976 (Reel 12, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/11/1976; 20/11/1976
    - Chang Seng Nong, 21/12/1976 (Reel 17, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 6/11/1976; 7/11/1976; 9/11/1976; 8/11/1976; 10/11/1976
    - Chao Hoeurn, N/A (Reel 20, Frame 47)
      Dates of Confessions: 7/1/1969
    - Chap Bun Thoeurn, 8/12/1975 (Reel 13, Frame 19)
    - Chap Chea, N/A (Reel 19, Frame 31)
    - Chap Chorn, 5/11/1975 (Reel 19, Frame 21)
    - Chap Ean, 13/10/1978 (Reel 23, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/1978
    - Chap Hey, 15/4/1978 (Reel 22, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/6/1978
    - Chap Hun, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 7)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/5/1977
    - Chap Lai, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/5/1977
    - Chap Mit, 25/9/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/10/1977; 3/12/1977; 31/1/1978; 3/1978
    - Chap Nam, 19/7/1977 (Reel 5, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/9/1977; 25/10/1977
    - Chap Ok, 18/3/1978 (Reel 11, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 31/3/1977
    - Chap Phap, 5/11/1975 (Reel 7, Frame 2)
    - Chap Voeurn, N/A (Reel 12, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 18/10/1977
    - Charieng Nokrase, 6/5/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 24)
    - Charoun Nokrase, 6/5/1976 (Reel 185, Frame 25)
      Nationality (if foreign): Thaas (Plate) Island
    - Chau (Chay) Kong, 7/4/1978 (Reel 186, Frame 39)
    - Chau Kort, 28/11/1975 (Reel 13, Frame 16)
    - Chau Kut, 12/6/1976 (Reel 22, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/6/1976; 25/6/1976;26/6/1976; 28/6/1976;29; 6/1976; 9/7/1976; 20/7/1976; 7/1976
    - Chau Ly Kim, 30/3/1976 (Reel 13, Frame 25)
    - Chau Moeung, 4/2/1978 (Reel 5, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 16/12/1977; 30/1/1978
    - Chau Ro, 22/12/1976 (Reel 23, Frame 5)
      Dates of Confessions: 22/12/1976
    - Chau Savann, 22/11/1977 (Reel 13, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 5/1/1977; 13/1/1978
    - Chau Sokal, N/A (Reel 13, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/7/1977
    - Chau Van, 4/9/1977 (Reel 10, Frame 2)
      Age: 37
      Dates of Confessions: 22/5/1978; 15/3/1976; 22/8/1977; 21/9/1977; 22/5/1978; 15/5/1978
      5/3/1977; 17/10/1977; 5/9/1977; 8/9/1977; 8/1/1978; 21/9/1977; 20/9/1977; 1 section undated
    - Chaun Maing, 12/11/1978 (Reel 18, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/1/1979
    - Chay Chev, 12/8/1977 (Reel 13, Frame 14)
      Dates of Confessions: 11/10/1977; 24/8/1977
    - Chay Kheam, N/A (Reel 11, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 28/6/1977
    - Chay Sovanna, 4/8/1975 (Reel 19, Frame 13)
    - Chea Bao, 2/2/1975 (Reel 6, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/4/1975; 29/4/1975; 4 sections undated
    - Chea Bun, N/A (Reel 5, Frame 12)
      Dates of Confessions: 13/11/1976; 21/11/1976; 15/11/1976; 8/12/1976; 20/1/1977; 22/1/1977; 20/1/1977
    - Chea Bun Cheng, 12/11/1977 (Reel 18, Frame 23)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/2/1978
    - Chea Chay, 18/1/1978 (Reel 13, Frame 13)
    - Chea Chhai, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 25)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/6/1977
    - Chea Choeurn, 17/9/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 2/10/1977
    - Chea Hoeurn, 26/11/1976 (Reel 13, Frame 21)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/2/1978; 2/11/1978
    - Chea Hoeurng, 21/11/1976 (Reel 8, Frame 8)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/11/1976; 27/11/1976; 29/11/1976; 30/11/1976; 1/12/1976
      2/12/1976; 13/12/1976/
    - Chea Hon, 27/9/1978 (Reel 21, Frame 29)
      Dates of Confessions: 19/10/1978
    - Chea Hout, 27/8/1978 (Reel 18, Frame 40)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/9/1978
    - Chea Huon, 22/5/1978 (Reel 13, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/5/1978; 1/6/1978; 29/6/1978
    - Chea Huon, 4/8/1977 (Reel 21, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 25/6/1977; 8/7/1977; 2/8/1977; 12/8/1977; 18/8/1977
    - Chea Kak, 25/3/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 16)
      Dates of Confessions: 21/4/1978; 29/4/1978
    - Chea Ke, 30/1/1978 (Reel 20, Frame 42)
      Dates of Confessions: 1/2/1978; 20/2/1978
    - Chea Khan, 2/1/1977 (Reel 11, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/2/1977; 23/2/1977; 13/2/1977; 13/2/1977
    - Chea Lang, N/A (Reel 22, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/6/1978; 9/7/1978
    - Chea Man, 11/1977 (Reel 20, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 9/11/1977
    - Chea Mao, 8/1977 (Reel 17, Frame 22)
      Dates of Confessions: 27/9/1977
    - Chea May, 17/11/1978 (Reel 17, Frame 13)
      Dates of Confessions: 29/11/1978
    - Chea Meach, 23/1/1977/ (Reel 19, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/3/1977
    - Chea Meng, N/A (Reel 6, Frame 1)
      Dates of Confessions: 23/12/1978
    - Chea Mong, N/A (Reel 23, Frame 19)
    - Chea Na, 20/9/1978 (Reel 21, Frame 30)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/9/1978
    - Chea Nay Sim, 9/6/1977 (Reel 19, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/2/1978
    - Chea Near, N/A (Reel 18, Frame 9)
      Dates of Confessions: 24/11/1977
    - Chea Nim, 13/1/1978 (Reel 17, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 14/3/1978
    - Chea Noeng, 7/9/1977 (Reel 12, Frame 18)
      Dates of Confessions: 26/11/1977
    - Chea Non, 4/1977 (Reel 13, Frame 33)
      Dates of Confessions: 4/5/1977; 21/4/1977; 1/5/1977; 10/5/1977; 21/5/1977; 22/4/1977; 23/4/1977
      15/4/1977; 28/3/1977; 26/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 24/3/1977; 24/3/1977
      8/4/1977; 21/2/1977; 8/4/1977; 29/4/1977; 20/2/1977
    - Chea Ny, N/A (Reel 16, Frame 27)
      Dates of Confessions: 10/877; 9/8/1977; 9/8/1977
    - Chea Oeuen, 11/1977 (Reel 12, Frame 15)
      Dates of Confessions: 30/12/1977
    - Chea Oeurn, 1/20/1977 (Reel 16, Frame 9)
    - Chea Pa, 8/3/1977 (Reel 10, Frame 11)
      Dates of Confessions: 20/5/1977
    - Chea Pech, 20/6/1978 (Reel 16, Frame 7)